<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Small Group Notes</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Small Group Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.143.1</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Faithfulness in Leadership and Marriage</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Faithfulness to God is reflected in our worship, leadership, and
relationships—especially in marriage. God calls us to honor Him with our actions and guard our
hearts from compromise.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="icebreaker-whats-the-best-piece-of-advice-youve-ever-been-given-about-relationships">Icebreaker: What’s the best piece of advice you’ve ever been given about relationships,&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>marriage, or commitment? Or, What’s the worst piece of relationship advice you’ve ever heard?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:1-2. Why is God so serious about honoring His name?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:5-6. What qualities made Levi a godly leader?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:8. How can spiritual leaders cause others to stumble?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:10-11. What does faithfulness to God have to do with how we treat others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:14. Why does God call marriage a covenant?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Malachi 2:15-16. What does it mean to &amp;ldquo;guard yourselves in your spirit&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="prayer-focus">Prayer Focus&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>For our worship – That we would honor God with our actions, not just words.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For faithfulness – That we would be trustworthy in leadership, relationships, and
commitments.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For marriages – That God would strengthen and restore marriages in our church.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For protection from compromi&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title>God’s Love &amp; Our Worship: Honoring the Faithful One</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/MAL.1.ESV">Malachi 1&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>How have you personally experienced God’s love, even when you didn’t
deserve it?
Next Step: Spend time this week thanking God for specific ways He has shown His love to you.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are some ways people (including ourselves) offer God &amp;ldquo;half-hearted
sacrifices&amp;rdquo; today?
Next Step: Identify one area of your life where you have been offering God less than your best and
commit to change this week.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why do you think God desires our sincere devotion rather than empty rituals?
Next Step: Be intentional this week about worshiping God with sincerity. Before praying, singing, or
serving, take a moment to align your heart with God.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In what ways do we sometimes treat worship as a burden rather than a joy?
Next Step: Reflect on your attitude toward worship and find one way to make it a joy this week (e.g.,
prepare ahead for Sunday, listen to worship music, or serve in a new way).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What would change in your life if you truly viewed your time, talents, and
treasures as offerings to God?
Next Step: Make a specific plan to use your time, talents, or treasures in a way that honors God this
week.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can we, as a church, encourage one another toward wholehearted
worship?
Next Step: Reach out to one person in your church this week to encourage them in their walk with God.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="prayer-focus">Prayer Focus:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Individually: Pray for God to reveal areas where you need to give Him your best, and ask for a
heart of joyful worship.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Corporately: Pray that our church would not offer God half-hearted worship but would be a
people who honor Him with sincerity and passion.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Reach out to one person in your church this week to encourage them in their walk with God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Folly of Not Trusting the Lord</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What’s one big decision or moment in your life when you had to rely on someone else’s
instructions or guidance? How did it feel to trust them, and did it turn out the way you
expected?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You must trust God even when you don’t want to trust Him.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/PRO.3.ESV">Deuteronomy 1:19-21, 26&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Read 1:26-27: How does fear distort our view of God’s character, and why is this so
dangerous?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read 1:28-33: Why is it easier to focus on obstacles than on God’s power? What
does this reveal about our faith?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read 1:34-35, 40: How does disobedience show a lack of trust in God, and what are the
consequences of disobedience in our lives?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read 1:42-44: Why is presumption (acting without God) so dangerous, and how is it
different from genuine faith?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read: 1:30; John 14:1: How does this passage ultimately point us to Christ, and why
is He the answer to our failure to trust God?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Identify one tangible way you can demonstrate trust in God this week by stepping outside
your comfort zone. Maybe it’s having a difficult conversation, saying yes to something He’s
calling you to, or surrendering control in a specific area of your life. Write it down as a
commitment and ask someone in the group to pray for you as you take this step. At the end
of the week, reflect on how taking action grew your faith and prepared you to trust Him more
in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trust The Lord Week 2</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you could instantly trust one thing completely, what would it be? Why?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You must trust God especially when you face challenges.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/2KI.18.ESV">2 Kings 18:1-6&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What does it mean to trust in God’s character, and how does knowing Him deepen
that trust?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How do you respond with your faith is challenged by doubt, fear, or opposition?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What can we learn from Hezekiah’s prayer in 2 Kings 19:14-19 about how to
approach God in times of crisis?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does God’s deliverance in 2 Kings 19:32-37 demonstrate His sovereignty and
power? How can this strengthen your faith?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are some practical ways you can demonstrate trust in God daily, especially in
difficult situations?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Identify one practical way to trust God in a current situation and share it with someone who
can pray for you and hold you accountable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trust The Lord</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What’s one thing you find hard to share or let someone else take control of (e.g., driving the
car, choosing the restaurant, planning an event)? Why is it hard to let go?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You must trust God.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.7.ESV">Proverbs 3:5-6&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What does it mean to trust in the Lord with all your heart? Why do you think God requires
complete trust?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why do you think we often rely on our own understanding instead of trusting God? Can
you share a time when this happened to you or someone you know?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does &amp;ldquo;acknowledge Him in all your ways&amp;rdquo; look like in everyday life? Why do you
think there are areas of your life where it’s harder to involve Him?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does the truth that God will make your paths straight encourage you in uncertain
times?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What do you find most challenging about living out trust and surrender in the Christian
life?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Take time this week to list specific promises of God that remind you why He is trustworthy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Because They Feared God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="read">Read&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EXO.1.ESV">Exodus 1:15-21&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h3>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Do you find the story of the Hebrew midwives (Ex 1:15-21) inspiring? If so, why?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Martin Luther and other reformers contrasted “servile fear” with “filial fear.” What do you remember about this distinction from the message? Why does this matter?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read together &lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/LUK.22.ESV">Luke 22:39-46&lt;/a>. Then read again verse 42. How are Christ’s words in this verse a pattern for believers?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read together &lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/PSA.130.ESV">Psalm 130&lt;/a>. Then read again verses three and four. How does God’s forgiveness enable Christians to have the right kind of fear of Him?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h3 id="prayer-focus">Prayer Focus&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Pray for babies at risk of dying by abortion, that God would spare them.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Pray for mothers and fathers considering abortion, that they would turn away from it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Pray that God would show us how we can help those in need.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Pray that the Spirit would enable us to live in the fear of the Lord.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Romans: The Struggle is Real</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What’s a product or gadget you once thought would make life easier but ended up being more
trouble than it was worth?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The struggle with sin is undeniable, but you are not without hope.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.7.ESV">Romans 7:13-25&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Why does Paul emphasize that sin, not the law, is the source of death (v. 13)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Paul mean by, “I do not do what I want, but I do the very thing I hate” (v. 15)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why does Paul say, “Nothing good dwells in me, that is, in my flesh” (v. 18)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Paul mean by “Who will deliver me from this body of death?” (v. 24), and how
does his answer (v. 25) bring hope?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does this passage prepare us for the hope and freedom described in Romans 8?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Reflect on a specific struggle with sin and surrender it to God in prayer, trusting in His strength.
Memorize Romans 7:25 to remind yourself of the victory found in Christ, and encourage someone
this week by sharing how God is working in your life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: What’s Law Got to Do With It?</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What’s the most ridiculous or unexpected rule you’ve ever had to follow?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God’s law is good.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.7.ESV">Romans 7:7-12&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>How does Paul’s statement, &amp;ldquo;I would not have known what sin was except through the law&amp;rdquo;
(Romans 7:7), challenge our understanding of sin before we encounter God&amp;rsquo;s Word?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Romans 7:8. Why do you think sin takes advantage of the law to provoke more sin?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Romans 7:9, What does Paul mean by &amp;ldquo;I died&amp;rdquo; in this context?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does Paul’s statement that &amp;ldquo;sin, seizing the opportunity through the commandment,
deceived me, and through the commandment killed me&amp;rdquo; (Romans 7:11) shed light on the
deceptive power of sin?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In Romans 7:12, Paul says, “So then, the law is holy, and the commandment is holy, righteous,
and good.” How can we reconcile the fact that the law reveals sin but is still described as
“holy, righteous, and good”?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Recognize that the law, though good, exposes the depth of your sin. Spend time reflecting on how
God&amp;rsquo;s commands have revealed areas where you have fallen short, whether in thoughts,
attitudes, or actions. Repent of these areas, acknowledging your need for God’s forgiveness and
grace.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: A Tale of Two Masters</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every Christian is a slave.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.6.ESV">Romans 6:15-23&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye-
opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Paul mean in Romans 6:15 when he asks, “Shall we sin because we are not
under the law but under grace?”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does Paul use the analogy of slavery in verses 16-18? What does it mean to be a
“slave to righteousness”?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse 21, Paul asks, “What benefit did you reap at that time from the things you are
now ashamed of?” How does this question help us understand the consequences of sin?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Romans 6:23 states, “For the wages of sin is death, but the gift of God is eternal life in
Christ Jesus our Lord.” How does this verse summarize the message of the passage, and
why is it significant?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This week, spend a few minutes each day reading Romans 6:15-23 and ask God to deepen your
understanding of being “alive to God” and “enslaved to righteousness.” Reflect on how you can
actively live out this truth in your daily choices. Try sharing one insight or change you’ve
experienced with someone who could encourage you in this journey.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: United with Christ</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every believer is united with Christ for a purpose.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Romans &lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.6.ESV">6:5-11&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye-
opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>How do secular and biblical perspectives on identity differ?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What does it mean to be “united with Christ” as described by Paul in verses five through
eleven?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>On two occasions, Paul said “we know” (vs. 6, 9). He clearly wanted us to not only know
about our union with Christ but to embrace the reality of that union. Sometimes we don’t
feel as if these things are true, so what role does faith play in our new identity in Christ?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: The Purpose of Grace</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Christians do not take advantage of God’s grace; we are transformed by God’s grace.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.6.ESV">Romans 6:1-4&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eyeopening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How would you explain the difference between being transformed by God&amp;rsquo;s grace and
taking advantage of it?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Romans 6:1-2. Why does Paul ask, &amp;ldquo;Shall we go on sinning so that grace may
increase?&amp;rdquo; How does this challenge any misconceptions about grace?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>According to Romans 6:3-4, how does being united with Christ in His death and
resurrection empower us to live a new life?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does it mean to &amp;ldquo;walk in newness of life&amp;rdquo; as stated in verse 4? How does grace make
this possible?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Consider how your small group can support each other to embrace the transformative power of grace and
live in righteousness. Discuss this as you conclude your group time this week.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: Two Men, Two Outcomes, One Hope</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/autumn/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Jesus restores what Adam destroyed.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.5.ESV">Romans 5:15-21&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye-
opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What is the main contrast between Adam&amp;rsquo;s trespass and Christ&amp;rsquo;s gift in Romans 5:15?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Paul mean when he says that “grace reigns through righteousness” in Romans
5:21?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does understanding Adam as a &amp;ldquo;type&amp;rdquo; of Christ help us grasp the significance of
Christ’s work (Romans 5:14, 18-19)?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Let grace, not guilt or fear, reign in your life. Consider how you can allow God’s grace to shape
your attitudes, decisions, and relationships. When faced with temptation or difficulty, remind
yourself that you are no longer under the reign of sin and death, but under the reign of grace.
Actively seek to reflect Christ’s righteousness in your daily life, extending grace to others as you
have received it from God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: God’s Justifying Work</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The work of God changes the focus and attitude of His people.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.5.ESV">Romans 5:1-11&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>How does understanding our justification by faith change our perspective on difficult
circumstances?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What role does &amp;ldquo;peace with God&amp;rdquo; play in changing our attitude toward life’s challenges?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can the hope of sharing in God’s glory influence our focus in daily life?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In what ways does God’s love, demonstrated through Christ’s sacrifice, transform our attitudes
toward ourselves and others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why would God allow us to suffer even while actively working in our lives?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When you encounter difficult circumstances, practice &amp;ldquo;preaching the gospel to yourself.&amp;rdquo; This involves
intentionally recalling God’s promises, Christ’s sacrifice, and the hope of eternal glory. Write down key
verses, like Romans 5:1-5, and keep them handy for quick reference throughout the day. By doing this,
you will train your mind to focus on God’s truth rather than on the challenges, which will transform
your attitude and response to trials. When we come back together in October we can share our scripture reference sheets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: Faith in God’s Promise</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You can count on God’s promises!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.4.ESV">Romans 4:13-25&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What does Paul mean when he says that Abraham&amp;rsquo;s promise did not come through the law but through the righteousness of faith (Romans 4:13)?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>How does Paul describe Abraham&amp;rsquo;s faith in verses 19-21, and what can we learn from it about trusting God&amp;rsquo;s promises?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: The Scripture Says</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.4.ESV">Romans 4:01-13&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What did Abraham and his legacy mean to the Jewish people and what was Paul&amp;rsquo;s purpose of bringing him up in this passage?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How did Abraham exhibit faith in Genesis 15:4-11?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Abraham&amp;rsquo;s sinfulness reveal to us?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verses 5 and 6, what does the phrase &amp;ldquo;God counts/imputes righteousness&amp;rdquo; mean?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are the conditions if any of God imputing his righteousness?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Scripture explains that righteousness is a gift for all people. How does this help us understand God&amp;rsquo;s heart for the lost?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Continue working on the prayer challenge! We are roughly 3 hours behind this week, but there&amp;rsquo;s still time to catch up! We have a weekly goal of ~9 hours.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans: The Foolishness of Boasting</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.3.ESV">Romans 3:27-31&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>In what ways do you see self-righteousness manifest in your life? How do you battle your
self-righteous tendencies?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why is it important to recognize that faith itself is not what saves us but rather the work
of Jesus Christ?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does Romans 3:29-30 emphasize the unity of Jews and Gentiles in terms of faith?
What implications does this have for how we view others in our faith community and
beyond?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In Romans 3:31, Paul states, &amp;ldquo;Do we then overthrow the law by this faith? By no means!
On the contrary, we uphold the law.&amp;rdquo; How can we reconcile the role of the law with the
principle of justification by faith? How should our understanding of the law change in light
of being justified by faith?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It’s important that we continually recognize the grace and mercy God has shown us. Instead of
buying into the false notion that we are basically good people, consider the truth that God has
saved you through faith in the person and work of His Son and focus on putting aside all boasting
so that you may only exalt God in and through your life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Serve: Fit for Service</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EPH.4.ESV"> Ephesians 4:17-24&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="small-group-discussion">Small Group Discussion&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>This week concluded this mini-series, which was an extension of the original “Serve the
Lord” series from January of this year. What will you stick with you from these messages on
Christian service?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does Paul mean when he says that the Gentiles walk in the “futility of their minds” (vs.
17)? Why are their minds this way?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse 19, Paul notes that the Gentiles “have become callous,” giving themselves up to sin.
What can we do to seek not to be similarly callous?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse 23, Paul directs Christians to “be renewed in the spirit of your minds.” Read also
Rom 12:1-2. What does it mean to be “renewed” this way? How do we pursue it?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Consider ways you can enrich your personal and corporate study of the Word of God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Serve: Engage Your Mind</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/PSA.32.ESV">Psalm 32&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="small-group-discussion">Small Group Discussion&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What stood out to you from the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>This week’s message focused on a psalm. Is there a psalm you have found to be particularly
meaningful in your walk with the Lord?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Many people today fail to acknowledge with their minds what is true. What are some
examples of this?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Reread Psalm 32:8-9. What is the contrast between humans and animals in these verses?
Why is this significant?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How might a failure to engage your mind affect your service to God?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Throughout the week, reflect on the many blessings which come from the gift God has
given humankind of minds to reason and understand.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Gift of Others in the Word</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>[Ephesians 4:1-16]&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="small-group-discussion">Small Group Discussion&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What stood out to you in this week’s message? What was good, helpful, convicting, troubling,
or led to more questions for you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why is it so important for each believer to know the Word?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why do you think it is hard for many professing believers to be faithfully involved in a church
or place themselves in a position to hear the Word taught?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>From the message what was the difference between Apostles and Prophets and Evangelists,
Shepherds and Teachers?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>We are called to grow in our faith and knowledge so that we are not carried away by every
wind of doctrine, by human cunning, by craftiness in deceitful schemes. Describe some of the
false doctrines, human cunning, craftiness, and deceitful schemes you see in the world and
even churches today.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Invite and encourage others at CrossPointe who don’t already attend an Adult
Bible Education class to attend one with you or to come to Wednesday night Bible Study.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Serve the Lord: Equipped with the Word</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/summer/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="called-through-the-word-to-the-word">Called through the Word to the Word&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="scripture">Scripture:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EPH.4.ESV">Ephesians 4:1-16&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What stood out to you in this week’s message? What was good, helpful, convicting, troubling, or led to more questions for you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why is the Word of God so important?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why do you think it can be so difficult for believers to be unified?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What is the attitude Paul says the church is to have towards one another?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Paul says we are to speak the truth in love. How is this often handled incorrectly and share an example (real or fictional) or how this should look in the church.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>How much time do you spend in the Word? If you think you should be spending more time studying the Word make a plan this week to follow through on it and possibly use your group to help keep you on track.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Unavoidable Court Date</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every person deserves to be judged by God.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.2.ESV">Romans 2:1-4&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>How does Romans 2:1-4 address the issue of self-righteous judgment?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What role does God&amp;rsquo;s kindness play in His judgment according to Romans 2:4?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does Paul address moralists in Romans 2:1-3, and what broader message does he convey about sin and judgment through this approach?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What warning does the sermon give about presuming upon God&amp;rsquo;s mercy, and what should be our correct response to God&amp;rsquo;s patience and kindness?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Consider how the awareness of your own guilt before God and the understanding of His mercy can transform your daily interactions and your overall perspective on life. Let this passage challenge you to live authentically, humbly acknowledging your need for grace and extending that grace to others.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When God gives up</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Those who oppose God invite destruction.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:19-32&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Romans 1:24-25 explains that God turns people over to their selfish desires due to their rejection of Him. How do these selfish desires manifest in today&amp;rsquo;s society, and what are some examples of how they lead to personal and societal destruction?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In Romans 1:26-27, Paul describes God turning people over to unnatural activities due to their opposition to Him. What are some contemporary examples of such activities, and how do they contribute to the moral decay and destruction in individuals&amp;rsquo; lives and society as a whole?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Romans 1:28-32 details how God turns people over to depraved thinking due to their persistent rejection of Him. How does this depraved thinking manifest in behavior, and what are the consequences for both individuals and communities?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Considering the progression described in Romans 1:24-32—from selfish desires to unnatural activities to depraved thinking—how can recognizing these stages help us understand the destructive path of opposing God?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It’s easy for us to begin to think that we are what’s right with society and, as a result, begin to despise those whose behavior is described in this passage. Yet, we must remain humble if we are to be compassionate and effective in sharing the gospel. This week, read and meditate on the message of 1 Corinthians 6:9-11.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Wrath of God pt. 2</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God’s wrath cannot be ignored.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:18&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Reflecting on the concept of God&amp;rsquo;s holiness, why do you think it&amp;rsquo;s challenging for humans to fully grasp the idea that God is both transcendent and morally pure? How does this understanding impact our view of sin and our relationship with God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ungodliness leads to unrighteousness. How do you see this progression playing out in your own life or in the world around you? What are some practical ways to guard against this downward spiral?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The sermon emphasizes that God&amp;rsquo;s wrath is rightly directed toward those who actively oppose Him and suppress the truth. How does this understanding of God&amp;rsquo;s wrath impact our perception of His mercy and patience? How can we reconcile God&amp;rsquo;s wrath and His love?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do you only talk about God’s love when trying to evangelize others? If so, think about how to effectively communicate God’s wrath and love to others this week.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Wrath of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God’s wrath cannot be ignored.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="(https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV)">Romans 1:18&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>In what ways do we see God&amp;rsquo;s wrath being revealed in the world today, and how does
this align with the depiction of God’s wrath in Romans 1:18?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Romans 1:18 states that God’s wrath comes from heaven against all godlessness and
wickedness of people who suppress the truth. How can we understand and explain the
justification of God&amp;rsquo;s wrath in a contemporary context where the idea of divine wrath
might be challenging or misunderstood?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does Paul establish that God&amp;rsquo;s wrath is not arbitrary but is directed specifically at
human actions that involve suppressing the truth? Discuss examples of how truth is
suppressed in society today and relate this to the concept of divine retribution.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Considering the nature of God&amp;rsquo;s wrath as revealed, justified, and rightly directed, how
should this influence the behavior and beliefs of Christians today? How can believers
reconcile the concept of a loving God with the reality of God&amp;rsquo;s wrath?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>How often do you think of God as a wrathful God? This week, consider the implications of God’s
wrath and thank Him that He has forgiven you and adopted you into His family.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Not Ashamed</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Everyone needs to hear the gospel.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:16-17&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h1>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>How does Paul describe the power of the gospel in Romans 1:16, and what implications does this have for how we view and share the gospel with others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Paul emphasizes that the gospel is for &amp;ldquo;everyone who believes&amp;rdquo; (Romans 1:16). How does this universal call to belief challenge or reinforce our understanding of who needs salvation and who can receive it?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Romans 1:17 states, &amp;ldquo;In it the righteousness of God is revealed from faith to faith.&amp;rdquo; How does understanding this righteousness as the righteousness God imputes to believers change our view of personal moral achievement and the basis of our salvation?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Considering that the gospel reveals both God&amp;rsquo;s power to save and man&amp;rsquo;s need for salvation, how should this dual revelation shape our understanding of evangelism and discipleship in relation to human responsibility and God&amp;rsquo;s sovereignty?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Is there someone you know who needs to hear the gospel? Will you commit to going to them as soon as possible to share the good news that they can be made right with God?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Compelled by Care</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Genuine care leads to action.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:8-15&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What stood out to you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse 8, Paul expresses gratitude for the faith of the Roman Christians. How does expressing gratitude for the faith of others contribute to building a strong Christian community?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse 10, Paul mentions his desire to visit the Roman Christians. What do you think motivated Paul&amp;rsquo;s desire to do so? How does face-to-face interaction impact our relationships with fellow believers and our ability to support and encourage one another?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Verse 11 speaks of Paul&amp;rsquo;s longing to impart some spiritual gift to the Romans to strengthen them. What do you think Paul means by &amp;ldquo;spiritual gift&amp;rdquo; in this context? How do spiritual gifts contribute to the growth and edification of the church today?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Paul expresses his eagerness to preach the gospel in Rome in verse 15. What do you think made Paul so eager to preach the gospel, even to those who were already believers? How can we cultivate a similar eagerness to share the gospel with others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verses 13-14, Paul states that he has often intended to visit Rome but has been prevented. Have you ever experienced obstacles or hindrances in serving God or fulfilling His purposes? How did you respond to these challenges, and what did you learn from them?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We care about many different things, and it’s very easy to become drawn away by the things that matter to us. As you spend time with the Lord this week, think about how your life reflects genuine care for others as it relates to the gospel.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Getting the Gospel Right</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The gospel is the good news that must be heard and understood.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:1-7&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was helpful, eye-opening,
or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verses 3-4, Paul describes God’s Son in two ways. How do those two ways relate to the
Old Testament, and why is this important?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The purpose of bringing about “the obedience of faith” is for “the sake of His name among
all nations” (1:5). How do you fit into this grand plan?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Name how this opening passage in Romans gives you confidence as a believer. Please
explain your answer.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>How much time do you spend reading and studying the Old Testament? As you consider Paul’s
greeting to the believers in Rome, consider its value and the impact that section of God’s Word
has made on your life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Romans #1: The Gospel of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/spring/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God’s purpose and plan are inevitable.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/ROM.1.ESV">Romans 1:1&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Paul called himself a slave, an apostle, and one who was set apart for the gospel of God. Which of these descriptions resonates most with you? Explain your answer.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why don’t genuine apostles still exist?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read 1:1-7 and 16:25-27. What similarities exist in those two passages? What themes do these verses reveal?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Name one or two things you hope to learn from our study in Romans.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Romans is one of the most important books in the Bible, and it is essential reading for every believer. This week, take inventory of your life and how willing you are to be used for God’s purpose and plan.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Judges</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="main-idea">Main Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Foolishness of Disregarding God Small Group Questions Judges
Disregarding God brings disastrous consequences&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="text">Text:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Judges 2:1-15&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What stood out to you, made you think, or was something that you liked, or remember from the sermon? Or What are you excited about, if anything, in studying the book of Judges?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How did the Israelites disregard God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>With consideration to question 2, how does it look for “modern day” Christians to disregard God in the same way?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Pastor Matt quoted his mother, “If you play with the pigs you’ll eventually end up smelling like them” what did she mean and how does or can that relate to us today and to this passage?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What were the three challenges that were given at the close of the message and how can we practically apply them to our lives today?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Examine question number 5 and search your life this week and ask the Holy Spirit to point out in your personal life where you need to apply this week&amp;rsquo;s message. Where are you disregarding God in your life and how can and will you change it?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Shrewd Stewardship</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Money holds no virtuous value, it simply is a means to an end. Money should not control our
hearts and lives but rather God should. Money then is a temporary gift that God gives us to serve him to
the absolute fullest measure we can in this life. We should steward our resources and money and use
them to serve others, the church, and the mission of the church is to further the kingdom of God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Guard the Good Deposit</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/2TI.1.ESV">2 Tim 1:8-14&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Who has God used to pass the good deposit on to you? How have they invested in you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Paul’s “trustworthy sayings”: 1 Timothy 1:15, 3:1, 4:8-9; 2 Timothy 2:11-13. What does his emphasis on sayings like these tell us about what it means to follow God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In 1 Timothy 4:16, Paul tells Timothy, “Keep a close watch on yourself and on the teaching.” Read this in context (start in verse 6). What practical tips does Paul give Timothy for how to keep a watch on himself and the teaching? How can you build these into your life?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are possible stumbling blocks that might prevent you from effectively passing on the good deposit to others?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Reach out to someone who has discipled you in the faith. Thank him or her, for sharing specific ways in which God has used this person in your life.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="prayer-focus">Prayer Focus&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If you’re already dicipleing others in the faith, ask God for continued wisdom so that your efforts will be even more effective.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you can’t think of anyone you’re mentoring, pray that God would show you people in your sphere of influence who would benefit from this. And pray that He would lead you as you begin to lead these individuals.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Take Care How You Build &amp; Life of a Steward</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="take-care-how-you-build">Take Care How You Build&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/1CO.3.ESV">1 Corinthians 3:10-15&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Malachi 1&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Where in this passage could you point to correct someone who suggests we are saved by works? What are some other passages of Scripture which more explicitly correct this thinking?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How should knowing that God will reward believers’ service affect how we live?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h1 id="life-of-a-steward">Life of a Steward&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A godly steward seeks to bring honor to God with everything&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Gifted to serve</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God gives people gifts with which they can serve Him.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/1CO.12.ESV">1 Corinthians 12:4-11&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This week&amp;rsquo;s discussion centers around spiritual gifts and using those gifts.
To help you identify the gifts you&amp;rsquo;ve been given if you don&amp;rsquo;t already know what yours are,
you can &lt;a href="https://groupleaders.org/curriculum-feed/spiritual-gift-assessment">take the assessment here&lt;/a>. Open the resource guide in another tab as you watch the video.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to go even further, you can also &lt;a href="https://groupleaders.org/curriculum-feed/spiritual-pathways-activity#personal-assessment">take the spiritual pathways test&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Attitude Affects Everything</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A godly servant must maintain the right attitude. Read: Luke 17:7-10&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye- opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Discuss instances in your life where maintaining the right attitude as a servant was challenging. How did you handle those situations?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can the principle of being a faithful and humble servant impact our relationships with others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Reflect on the concept of service without expecting recognition or reward. How can this mindset contribute to a godly attitude?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can we encourage one another in our journey to maintain the right attitude as godly servants?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This week, take the time to think about what attitude you most consistently display in serving the Lord.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Serve The Lord: Week 1</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2024/winter/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The Domino Effect
Those whom God has saved must serve Him.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Joshua &lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JOS.24.ESV">24:14-15&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eye- opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verses 1-13. What are some things that you find significant in those verses? Discuss what you’ve found and why those insights are important.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Joshua commanded the people to serve the Lord—are we under the same command? Why or why not?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Joshua made a choice for himself and his family and challenged Israel to do the same. If you choose not to serve the Lord, what does your choice reveal about your heart and life?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Luke 9:23. Is there a difference between serving and following Jesus? What does He say about serving Him on our terms?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Serve the Lord is the theme for 2024 at CrossPointe Church. Take inventory this week of your service to the Lord through the church.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Change of Plans</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Don’t be arrogant, Consider and Submit to God&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-james-413-17">Read: James 4:13-17&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JAS.4.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the
most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Why do you think people find it difficult to consider and include God in their daily plans?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What helpful habits do you think could help us remember and recognize God’s sovereignty
over our lives?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What does the “sin of omission” mean and what does it practically look like?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Galatians 4</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/GAL.4.ESV">Galatians 4:4-7&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Paul wrote that Jesus was born when the fullness of time had come. Discuss the implications of that statement. What does this teach us about God?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Paul noted that Jesus was born “to redeem those who were under the law.” What does this mean for those who are saved?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>According to the text, what has God done for those He has redeemed? How should this affect our lives?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>He Gives More Grace</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God’s grace changes God’s people.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-james-46-12">Read: James 4:6-12&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JAS.4.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon was the most helpful, eyeopening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>James issued eleven commands in this section. Which of these commands do you struggle
with the most?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verse seven. How do the actions of submitting to God and resisting the devil relate
to one another, and what are some ways you can resist the devil?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verse nine. Why is genuine repentance essential in our relationship with God? How can
we cultivate a repentant heart?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In verse twelve, James warns against judging others. What do you think he means by this?
How can we be discerning but not go over the line in our attitude and interactions with
others?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>How does God’s grace impact your life every day? Meditate on verses 7-10 this week and
evaluate how you respond to the grace you’ve received. And be sure to vote on Tuesday!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>No Time for Fussing and Fighting, My Friends</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Unchecked desires produce ungodly fruit.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-james-41-5">Read: James 4:1-5&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JAS.4.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon did you find to be the
most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>James wanted his readers to understand that selfishness—which is a result of adopting
worldly wisdom—will always destroy peace. Name some ways this is true in different
aspects of life.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One of the issues that James addresses in this text is that we are prone to covet or envy.
What is envy and how is this dangerous attitude expressed in your life and in our culture?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Thinking about the sermon last week and the text we’re studying this week, discuss some
practical ways you can address selfishness and envy in your life.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What does it mean to be a friend of the world? Why is it not possible to be friends with the
world and faithful to God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can the fact that God “years jealously” over you help you overcome the serious issues
that James addresses in this text?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We all struggle with selfishness and conflict. This week read through Galatians 5:22-26 and
think about how the Fruit of the Spirit helps us overcome the sins that cause conflict and
division.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Good Life</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The wisdom that guides your life cannot be hidden.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-james-31-12">Read: James 3:1-12&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JAS.3.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon did you find to be the
most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Provide examples of worldly and godly wisdom. How do we often confuse these two and
how often have you consulted worldly wisdom over the last month?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not all sources of wisdom are equally valid, so how do you determine what wisdom to
follow?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Most people search for wisdom in one of the following places: Senses-What I feel; Self-What I
think; Society-What others think; or Scripture-What God thinks. Which of these sources do you
depend on the most? If you said something other than Scripture, then how is it worldly in the
way that James describes?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Earthly wisdom is sensual and demonic. What do these words mean and how does this help
us recognize worldly wisdom?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verses 3:17-18. James lists eight traits of heavenly wisdom. Identify and define them
together as a group.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Godly wisdom is vital for believers to follow. Read Psalm 1:1-6 this week to discover where you
can find godly wisdom. Also, read 1 Corinthians 1:18-25 and consider how the cross of Christ is
the apex of wisdom.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Can That Faith Save? &amp; The Truth About The Tongue</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="last-week">Last week&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Any faith that does not produce works is worthless.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-james-214-26">Read: James 2:14-26&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JAS.2.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Define clearly the issue in 2:14. Why would people claim to have genuine faith if they
don’t? What might motivate this kind of deception (or self-delusion) in our world today?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>James attacks cold, intellectual belief in 2:19-20. Illustrate this kind of “heady” approach
to Christianity with a couple of modern examples. In what ways do you tend to
intellectualize rather than actualize your faith?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h1 id="this-week">This week&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea-1">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The things you say, matter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Faith That Serves All</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/autumn/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>One must learn to accept others, whatever their social status or class. He must show courtesy
to all, compassion for all, and consistency to all. Holding to the Faith in our Lord Jesus Christ, and fulfilling
the royal law are key in a faith that works.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="james-21-13">James 2:1-13&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My brothers, show no partiality as you hold the faith in our Lord Jesus Christ, the Lord of glory. 2 For if a
man wearing a gold ring and fine clothing comes into your assembly, and a poor man in shabby clothing
also comes in, 3 and if you pay attention to the one who wears the fine clothing and say, “You sit here in a
good place,” while you say to the poor man, “You stand over there,” or, “Sit down at my feet,” 4 have you not
then made distinctions among yourselves and become judges with evil thoughts? 5 Listen, my beloved
brothers, has not God chosen those who are poor in the world to be rich in faith and heirs of the kingdom,
which he has promised to those who love him? 6 But you have dishonored the poor man. Are not the rich the
ones who oppress you, and the ones who drag you into court? 7 Are they not the ones who blaspheme the
honorable name by which you were called? 8 If you really fulfill the royal law according to the Scripture, “You
shall love your neighbor as yourself,” you are doing well. 9 But if you show partiality, you are committing sin
and are convicted by the law as transgressors. 10 For whoever keeps the whole law but fails in one point has
become guilty of all of it. 11 For he who said, “Do not commit adultery,” also said, “Do not murder.” If you do
not commit adultery but do murder, you have become a transgressor of the law. 12 So speak and so act as
those who are to be judged under the law of liberty. 13 For judgment is without mercy to one who has shown
no mercy. Mercy triumphs over judgment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Beware!</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Beware of those who lie about Jesus.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/2JN.1.ESV">2 John 7-13&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon did you find to be the
most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Last week you were supposed to do a personal Bible study and look up all the instances
where the apostle John wrote that we are to love one another. Discuss what you found.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>John issued three commands in this text, the first is “watch yourselves” (v.8). How do you
watch yourselves to prevent falling prey to false teachers?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why is going beyond the Word of God so dangerous? Name some of the ways this
strategy has been used to lead people astray.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What is significant about verse twelve? Discuss how we should apply what John said to
those believers to our walk with Christ?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Next week we will begin to walk through the book of James. Please read the book of James
every day this week (5 chapters will take about 15-20 minutes) and prepare for this exciting
study.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Walking In Truth</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking In Truth
God’s people must walk in truth.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="(https://www.bible.com/bible/59/2JN.1.ESV)">2 John 4-6&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon did you find to be the most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Last week you were supposed to read 2 John and write out what you observed from the text. Discuss what you saw in your study of this short letter.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Have you ever learned a valuable lesson because you weren’t walking in truth? If you’re comfortable, share with your group what happened and what you learned.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>John said we are to love one another, what other &amp;ldquo;___ one another&amp;rdquo; commands are given throughout scripture?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why do you think John often repeats the command of our Lord to love one another?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do a personal Bible study this week and look up all the instances where the apostle John wrote that we are to love one another. Use a concordance or an online Bible study tool such as Logos free edition (&lt;a href="https://www.logos.com/free-edition">https://www.logos.com/free-edition&lt;/a>) to help you find what you need.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Truth and Love Together</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Those who know Jesus are united by truth.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/2JN.1.ESV">2 John 1-3&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What insight, principle, or observation from this week’s sermon did you find to be the most helpful, eye-opening, or troubling? Explain.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>John referred to himself as the elder, most likely referring to his status as an older man or mature believer and not to the office of elder. Name some reasons you think that is significant and what can we learn from that designation?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Most of us have a bias toward being either loving or truthful. Which characterizes you? How do you become more balanced?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Believers are to be united by truth, but we sometimes have different beliefs. How do we stay united within the church when we disagree?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>John said, “the truth will be with us forever.” Name some ways that statement encourages you or gives you hope.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Read 2 John every day this week and write down what you observe. Be prepared to discuss your observations in small group next week.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jude - Week 5</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="main-idea">Main Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You can trust that God is able to keep you from stumbling and present you blameless before
Him.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="jude-24-25">Jude 24-25&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>24 Now to him who is able to keep you from stumbling and to present you blameless before the
presence of his glory with great joy, 25 to the only God, our Savior, through Jesus Christ our
Lord, be glory, majesty, dominion, and authority, before all time and now and forever. Amen.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jude - Week 4</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker-question">Ice breaker question&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What is the best fruit?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="main-idea">Main Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Remember Warnings &amp;amp; Stand Firm in The Face of Danger&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="jude-17-23">Jude 17-23&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>17 But you must remember, beloved, the predictions of the apostles of our Lord Jesus Christ. 18 They said to you, &amp;ldquo;In the last time there will be scoffers, following their own ungodly passions.&amp;rdquo; 19 It is these who cause divisions, worldly people, devoid of the Spirit. 20 But you, beloved, building yourselves up in your most holy faith and praying in the Holy Spirit, 21 keep yourselves in the love of God, waiting for the mercy of our Lord Jesus Christ that leads to eternal life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jude - Week 3</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If Rebecca was a dessert, what would she be and why?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="main-idea">Main Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We must be active listeners to contend against apostasy&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="jude-1116">Jude 11–16&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JUD.1.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What stood out to you, made you think, or was something that you like, or remember
from the sermon?&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>What are some of the hidden reefs (hidden dangers) being preached in churches and
religions today? Why do you think people don’t see them?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Judgment and Character of Spiritual Counterfeits</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Believers in Christ need to remember the judgment of God on apostates, and be able to
identify them through their ungodly behavior and lifestyle, and contend with them concerning the faith.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="jude-5-10">Jude 5-10&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Now I want to remind you, although you once fully knew it, that Jesus, who saved a people out of
the land of Egypt, afterward destroyed those who did not believe. 6 And the angels who did not
stay within their own position of authority, but left their proper dwelling, he has kept in eternal
chains under gloomy darkness until the judgment of the great day— 7 just as Sodom and
Gomorrah and the surrounding cities, which likewise indulged in sexual immorality and pursued
unnatural desire, serve as an example by undergoing a punishment of eternal fire.
8 Yet in like manner these people also, relying on their dreams, defile the flesh, reject authority,
and blaspheme the glorious ones. 9 But when the archangel Michael, contending with the devil,
was disputing about the body of Moses, he did not presume to pronounce a blasphemous
judgment, but said, “The Lord rebuke you.” 10 But these people blaspheme all that they do not
understand, and they are destroyed by all that they, like unreasoning animals, understand
instinctively.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jude Week 1</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/summer/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="main-idea">Main Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As children of God, it is necessary to be alert and ready to stand on truth and proclaim the truth
in the midst of opposition and persecution.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Jude 1-4
(1) Jude, a servant of Jesus Christ and brother of James, To those who are called, beloved in God the
Father and kept for Jesus Christ: (2) May mercy, peace, and love be multiplied to you. (3) Beloved,
although I was very eager to write to you about our common salvation, I found it necessary to write
appealing to you to contend for the faith that was once for all delivered to the saints. (4) For certain
people have crept in unnoticed who long ago were designated for this condemnation, ungodly people,
who pervert the grace of our God into sensuality and deny our only Master and Lord, Jesus Christ. (ESV)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When God Brings Difficulties</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God often allows difficulties to expose the orientation of your heart.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-esther-51-14">Read: Esther 5:1-14&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EST.5.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Describe, in your own words, God’s sovereignty and discuss why this doctrine is viewed as
either troubling or comforting. How should we view God’s sovereignty, especially when
difficulties come?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Describe a time when you followed a plan that was determined by your will rather than
God’s Word. How did this turn out for you (and others)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How did Esther display courage in this text? Discuss what the Bible teaches about courage
and how this virtue should impact your life.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are some of the dangers of living for your personal joy and happiness? How can you
avoid these things?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In what ways can we feed idolatry in our lives rather than forsaking it?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Think about the difficulties you’ve experienced in your life and then consider how God has used
those things to shape and sanctify you. Write down three lessons you’ve learned through the
difficulties you’ve faced.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When Everything Changes</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God doesn’t need you, but He desires to use you for His purpose.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-esther-41-17">Read: Esther 4:1-17&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EST.4.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Describe a time the Lord directed you to do something, but you were full of fear rather
than faith and did not obey. Why is Esther 4 a good chapter for many of us who have
been in this position?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How does the gospel fuel obedience to God in the life of a believer?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mordecai didn’t hide his grief but displayed it publicly for all to see. Why do we tend to
conceal our grief or struggles rather than sharing them openly? What does the Bible say
about being honest with each other in our struggles?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>We are often hopeful that somebody in the church will step up to meet a need or create
an outreach ministry, why do you believe we continually hope someone else will do what
we see needs to be done?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Verses 15-17 uncover a substantial reversal from earlier in Esther’s story. Identify and
discuss what this reversal means for Esther’s development and how it applies to you
personally.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God desires to use you, not because you are perfect, not because you are highly gifted, not
because you are intelligent, wealthy, well-educated, or skillful. God desires to use you because
He is full of grace and mercy—it is an honor to be used by the King of Kings. This week read and
meditate on 1 Corinthians 1:26-31, then journal your thoughts about how this passage applies
to you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When Evil Takes the Stage</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Evil rises in the world around us, but God is always going before us.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-esther-31-15">Read: Esther 3:1-15&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EST.3.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Has there ever been a situation in your life when you’ve been passed over and someone
less deserving was promoted? How did you handle the disappointment? What are some
dangers you must be aware of that can poison your heart in those situations?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The king’s servants said Mordecai transgressed the king’s command when he refused to
bow to Haman. Do you believe Mordecai was right or wrong in refusing to bow? Explain
your answer from Scripture.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verses 7-11. What does the text reveal about King Ahasuerus? What should we
learn and apply from his response?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>How does this inform your decision making of what of leaders you look for or the kind of leader you yourself want to be?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When Compromise Catches Up</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Compromise with the world will always complicate the life of God’s people.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-esther-21-11">Read: Esther 2:1-11&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EST.2.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mordecai and Esther were caught by years of compromise and became like the Persians.
Discuss some of the ways are you most tempted to compromise with the world?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Verse six focuses our attention on the fact that the Jews were exiles in Persia. What are
some similarities believers share with exiles and in what ways is God’s grace given to
exiles?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Esther gained favor throughout this narrative (see, vs. 9,15,17). What can we assume
about Esther from the text? How does this apply to our lives in this world?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What character trait of Esther is revealed in verses 10 and 20? How does that trait impact
the story of Esther and what can we learn from her example?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This week, read 1 Peter 2:1-10; Revelation 1:6; Colossians 1:13; and Ephesians 4:1 and consider
what it means that you are a citizen of two kingdoms and what that means for how you live
daily? What responsibilities and hope has God given you?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>When God Tells A Story</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-34/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-34/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God is faithful to His promise, even when it seems He is absent.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/EST.1.ESV">Esther 1:1-22&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon the past two weeks?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There has been a massive increase in the number of people who do not believe in God and
claim no religious affiliation. Why do you believe so many people have a hard time
believing there is a God? What can we do to help others know God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>God is noticeably absent from the book of Esther, but He’s also very present and working
behind the scenes to accomplish His purpose. Discuss what you learned during a time in
your life when God seemed absent to you, but in hindsight you could see that God was
working behind the scenes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One of the purposes for describing the elaborate scene in chapter one is for the readers to
understand the greatness of the king and the pride that enveloped his life. Talk about
how does pride manifests itself in your life?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sometimes the outcome of the event contains the reason for the author including the
event itself. After the king listened to Memucan’s advice (Esther 1:16–20), what do we
now learn about Vashti? What do we now learn about Ahasuerus?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The king surrounded himself with “wise men who knew the times” (v.13). Talk about
whether their advice was good or foolish? Discuss the kind of people you surround
yourself with and look to for godly counsel.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="prayer-focus">Prayer Focus&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As you pray this week, be sure to thank God for giving you His wisdom in Scripture so that you
can wisely navigate life in a cursed world. Also, ask God for the strength to follow His wisdom
and reject the strong pull of the wisdom of the world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Living Savior</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>People need to hear about the promise of forgiveness through faith in the living Savior.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-john-2019-23">Read: John 20:19-23&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JHN.20.ESV">Bible app link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>John wrote that the disciples were locked in a room “for fear of the Jews” why were they
afraid and what significance did Jesus’ message of peace have for them?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jesus sent His disciples to continue the mission He was given by the Father and promised
to give them the Holy Spirit. In what ways does the Holy Spirit make us effective in
continuing the mission of Christ?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In what ways do we struggle to accept the promise of forgiveness through faith in Jesus
today, and what steps can we take to overcome those struggles?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How can we share the promise of forgiveness with others in our communities, especially
those who may be skeptical or resistant to the idea?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In your devotional time this week, consider the depth of forgiveness you’ve received through
faith in Christ. One way to accomplish this is to write a list of your sins each day in your journal.
Then, after writing down those sins, write the word FORGIVEN in bold letters over that list.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Praying Savior</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/spring/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What&amp;rsquo;s one skill or hobby you&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to learn, but haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to yet?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Jesus prays for the disciples because the Father delights to help His children.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-john-176-19">Read: John 17:6-19&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/JHN.17.ESV">Open Bible app&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What did Jesus pray for his disciples in this passage? Why do you think these requests are
significant?
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>How are we sanctified?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jesus prayed openly in front of His disciples so that they could hear what He was
requesting for them from the Father. What are some benefits of hearing someone carry
your burdens to Father in prayer?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jesus prays for his disciples&amp;rsquo; joy. How can our relationship with God and our faith in Jesus
bring us joy, even in difficult circumstances?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jesus was preparing His disciples for His departure and the mission they would carry out.
What are some truths that we can apply concerning the relationship between prayer and
any God-honoring endeavor?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ask a brother or sister you encounter this week from CrossPointe how you can pray for them
and then stop what you’re doing and openly ask God to meet their need at that moment.
Praying for someone when they can hear it is a way to foster the kind of relational intimacy God
desires among His people in the church.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Faithful and Wise Servant</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Being a faithful and wise servant, means you are prepared for the coming judgment. You are obeying Jesus’ commands to make disciples, and you are a good steward with all that he has provided you. Christ’s return is your hope and you are ready for the coming kingdom.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="matthew-2445-51">Matthew 24:45-51&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>For sake of context, &lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/MAT.24.ESV">we will read all of chapter 24&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>“Who then is the faithful and wise servant, whom his master has set over his household, to give them their food at the proper time? 46 Blessed is that servant whom his master will find so doing when he comes. 47 Truly, I say to you, he will set him over all his possessions. 48 But if that wicked servant says to himself, ‘My master is delayed,’ 49 and begins to beat his fellow servants and eats and drinks with drunkards, 50 the master of that servant will come on a day when he does not expect him and at an hour he does not know 51 and will cut him in pieces and put him with the hypocrites. In that place there will be weeping and gnashing of teeth.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Can You Have Eternal Life?</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ice-breaker">Ice Breaker:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What is something that you own that you would have a hard time giving
away?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Salvation is only possible because of the person and work of Jesus. Anyone
who is seeking eternal life must go to Jesus and simply repent of their sins and trust in
Him for salvation.
Jesus invites people to have life.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-matthew-1916-30">Read: Matthew 19:16-30&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>16 And behold, a man came up to him, saying, “Teacher, what good deed must I do to have eternal life?” 17 And he said to him, “Why do you ask me about what is good? There is only one who is good. If you would enter life, keep the commandments.” 18 He said to him, “Which ones?” And Jesus said, “You shall not murder, You shall not commit adultery, You shall not steal, You shall not bear false witness, 19 Honor your father and mother, and, You shall love your neighbor as yourself.” 20 The young man said to him, “All these I have kept. What do I still lack?” 21 Jesus said to him, “If you would be perfect, go, sell what you possess and give to the poor, and you will have treasure in heaven; and come, follow me.” 22 When the young man heard this he went away sorrowful, for he had great possessions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The cost of following Jesus - Zaccheus</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="read">Read&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Luke 19:1-10&lt;/p>
&lt;p>19 He entered Jericho and was passing through. 2 And behold, there was a man named Zacchaeus. He was a chief tax collector and was rich. 3 And he was seeking to see who Jesus was, but on account of the crowd he could not, because he was small in stature. 4 So he ran on ahead and climbed up into a sycamore tree to see him, for he was about to pass that way. 5 And when Jesus came to the place, he looked up and said to him, “Zacchaeus, hurry and come down, for I must stay at your house today.” 6 So he hurried and came down and received him joyfully. 7 And when they saw it, they all grumbled, “He has gone in to be the guest of a man who is a sinner.” 8 And Zacchaeus stood and said to the Lord, “Behold, Lord, the half of my goods I give to the poor. And if I have defrauded anyone of anything, I restore it fourfold.” 9 And Jesus said to him, “Today salvation has come to this house, since he also is a son of Abraham. 10 For the Son of Man came to seek and to save the lost.”&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The cost of following Jesus</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A follower of Christ will put Christ and his commandments above everyone including
self.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Matthew 10:34-39&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth. I have not come to bring peace, but a
sword. For I have come to set a man against his father, and a daughter against her mother, and
a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law. And a person’s enemies will be those of his own
household. Whoever loves father or mother more than me is not worthy of me, and whoever
loves son or daughter more than me is not worthy of me. And whoever does not take his cross
and follow me is not worthy of me. Whoever finds his life will lose it, and whoever loses his life
for my sake will find it. (ESV)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Great Invitation</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Jesus invites people to have life.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-john-737-39">Read: John 7:37-39&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>37 On the last day of the feast, the great day, Jesus stood up and cried out, “If anyone thirsts, let him come to me and drink. 38 Whoever believes in me, as[a] the Scripture has said, ‘Out of his heart will flow rivers of living water.’” 39 Now this he said about the Spirit, whom those who believed in him were to receive, for as yet the Spirit had not been given, because Jesus was not yet glorified.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Spiritual Transaction with the Creator of Heaven and Earth</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God is available and ready to hear His people who seek Him through prayer.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-psalm-51-12">Read: Psalm 5:1-12&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To the choirmaster: for the flutes. A Psalm of David.
5 Give ear to my words, O Lord;
consider my groaning.
2 Give attention to the sound of my cry,
my King and my God,
for to you do I pray.
3 O Lord, in the morning you hear my voice;
in the morning I prepare a sacrifice for you[a] and watch.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Life-Changing Desire</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Word of God is needed for spiritual life and development.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-1-peter-122-23">Read: 1 Peter 1:22-2:3&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>22 Having purified your souls by your obedience to the truth for a sincere brotherly love, love one another earnestly from a pure heart, 23 since you have been born again, not of perishable seed but of imperishable, through the living and abiding word of God; 24 for&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“All flesh is like grass
and all its glory like the flower of grass.
The grass withers,
and the flower falls,
25 but the word of the Lord remains forever.”&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Heart of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Seek the Lord instead of seeking after things, like those who have no hope.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-matthew-625-34">Read: Matthew 6:25-34&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>“Therefore I tell you, do not be anxious about your life, what you will eat or what you will drink, nor about your body, what you will put on. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothing? “Therefore do not be anxious about tomorrow, for tomorrow will be anxious for itself. Sufficient for the day is its own trouble. Look at the birds of the air: they neither sow nor reap nor gather into barns, and yet your heavenly Father feeds them. Are you not of more value than they? And which of you by being anxious can add a single hour to his span of life? And why are you anxious about clothing? Consider the lilies of the field, how they grow: they neither toil nor spin, yet I tell you, even Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these. But if God so clothes the grass of the field, which today is alive and tomorrow is thrown into the oven, will he not much more clothe you, O you of little faith? Therefore do not be anxious, saying, ‘What shall we eat?’ or ‘What shall we drink?’ or ‘What shall we wear?’ For the Gentiles seek after all these things, and your heavenly Father knows that you need them all. But seek first the kingdom of God and his righteousness, and all these things will be added to you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Grace of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">Announcements&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Church office is closed Wednesday and Thursday&lt;/li>
&lt;li>No Mid-Week Activities on Campus this week&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Children’s Christmas Program is December 4th&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Church vote on 2023 spending plan is December 4th&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The grace of God is required for life and godliness.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-titus-211-15">Read: Titus 2:11-15&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For the grace of God has appeared, bringing salvation for all people, 12training us to renounce ungodliness and worldly passions, and to live self-controlled, upright, and godly lives in the present age, 13waiting for our blessed hope, the appearing of the glory of our great God and Savior Jesus Christ, 14who gave himself for us to redeem us from all lawlessness and to purify for himself a people for his own possession who are zealous for good works.
15Declare these things; exhort and rebuke with all authority. Let no one disregard you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>More Than Knowledge</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">Announcements&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>November 20th: Christmas Decorating after Morning Worship.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>November 23rd: Church offices are closed and there are no mid-week activities.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Christmas Eve: Services at 4:00 and 6:00 pm.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Right teaching leads to right living which displays the truth and beauty of the gospel.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-titus-21-10">Read: Titus 2:1-10&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>But as for you, teach what accords with sound doctrine. 2Older men are to be sober-minded, dignified, self-controlled, sound in faith, in love, and in steadfastness. 3Older women likewise are to be reverent in behavior, not slanderers or slaves to much wine. They are to teach what is good, 4and so train the young women to love their husbands and children, 5to be self-controlled, pure, working at home, kind, and submissive to their own husbands, that the word of God may not be reviled. 6Likewise, urge the younger men to be self-controlled. 7Show yourself in all respects to be a model of good works, and in your teaching show integrity, dignity, 8and sound speech that cannot be condemned, so that an opponent may be put to shame, having nothing evil to say about us. 9Bondservants are to be submissive to their own masters in everything; they are to be well-pleasing, not argumentative, 10not pilfering, but showing all good faith, so that in everything they may adorn the doctrine of God our Savior.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Men Who Must Speak &amp; The Men Who Must Be Silenced</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">Announcements&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Vote on Tuesday!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>2023 Budget Presentation after morning worship on November 13th.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Church Christmas Decorating: November 20th after morning worship.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A well-ordered church is led by elders who teach and protect God’s people.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-titus-15-16">Read: Titus 1:5-16&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is why I left you in Crete, so that you might put what remained into order, and appoint elders in every town as I directed you— 6if anyone is above reproach, the husband of one wife, and his children are believers and not open to the charge of debauchery or insubordination. 7For an overseer, as God’s steward, must be above reproach. He must not be arrogant or quick-tempered or a drunkard or violent or greedy for gain, 8but hospitable, a lover of good, self-controlled, upright, holy, and disciplined. 9He must hold firm to the trustworthy word as taught, so that he may be able to give instruction in sound doctrine and also to rebuke those who contradict it.
10For there are many who are insubordinate, empty talkers and deceivers, especially those of the circumcision party. 11They must be silenced, since they are upsetting whole families by teaching for shameful gain what they ought not to teach. 12One of the Cretans, a prophet of their own, said, “Cretans are always liars, evil beasts, lazy gluttons.” 13This testimony is true. Therefore rebuke them sharply, that they may be sound in the faith, 14not devoting themselves to Jewish myths and the commands of people who turn away from the truth. 15To the pure, all things are pure, but to the defiled and unbelieving, nothing is pure; but both their minds and their consciences are defiled. 16They profess to know God, but they deny him by their works. They are detestable, disobedient, unfit for any good work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Well-Built Life</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">Announcements&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Men and Women in Prayer is this Saturday at 8:30am&lt;/li>
&lt;li>November 6th: Lord’s Supper and Fall-Back Sunday&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God can be trusted; therefore, your life can be built on who God is and what God has
done.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-titus-11-4">Read: Titus 1:1-4&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read vs. 1. Paul identified himself as a “servant of God and an apostle of Jesus
Christ.” Why do you believe these two titles are significant and what does this
teach us about our identity?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read vs. 2. What does the fact that God cannot lie reveal? How does this aspect
of God’s nature affect or encourage you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Paul called Titus his “true child”—what can we learn from the relationship
between Titus and Paul?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>What do you hope to learn from our study in Titus? Take time this week to read through
this short letter and write down three things you want God to do in your life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The End of the Matter</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">Announcements&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>• Faith Promise Commitment Sunday is next Sunday. We will not be collecting
commitment cards, but we do ask that you and your family will commit to help fund
our mission efforts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• Secure the Knot is this coming Saturday. October 23rd is the last day to register for
this important event.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Life under the sun is complex but doesn’t have to be complicated if you fear God and
obey His commandments.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rejoice and Remember</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="announcements">ANNOUNCEMENTS&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Mission Emphasis next Sunday. Please get food truck tickets only if you’re
planning to stay for the missionary presentations after lunch.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Secure the Knot is Saturday, October 29. Please sign up by the end of this
week—cost is $30.00 per couple and is a small but great investment in your
marriage.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Faith Promise Commitment Sunday is October 30. Pray about how much you will
generously give to support CrossPointe’s mission program for the next 12 months.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Whether you are young or old, enjoy life because death is coming.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rejoice and Remember - Supplement</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3-supplement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3-supplement/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="question-3">Question 3&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Once again the Preacher is honest about the troubles of life, both physical
and psychological. He also has some advice for us: we should do what we
can to remove discouragement from our souls and to minimize damage to
our bodies. This is not a call to deny the very real suffering that everyone
experiences. Nor is it a call to escape pain by living for pleasure. Rather, it is
a call to take care of our mental and physical health.
If we are getting discouraged by various vexations, and if we are tempted
therefore to become depressed or disillusioned, we should do what the
Preacher says and remove those vexations from our hearts. This starts with
refusing to feel sorry for ourselves. Rather than dwelling on all the things
that are going wrong, we should count our blessings. We should also seek
the care of a pastor or the counsel of Christian friends—brothers and sisters
in Christ who are sympathetic to our situation but also able to see our
situation for what it is and tell us what we need to hear, especially from the
Scriptures.
But the very best remedy for vexation is to go to God in prayer, telling him
all our troubles. “Do not be anxious about anything”—or vexed about
anything, we might say—“but in everything by prayer and supplication with
thanksgiving let your requests be made known to God.” This command is
then followed by a promise: “And the peace of God, which surpasses all
understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds in Christ Jesus”
(Philippians 4:6–7). The Biblical way of removing vexation is to cast our
cares on God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What You Don’t Know Can Hurt You</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Incomplete knowledge is not always a reason for inaction.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-ecclesiastes-111-6">Read: Ecclesiastes 11:1-6&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Cast your bread upon the waters,
for you will find it after many days.
2 Give a portion to seven, or even to eight,
for you know not what disaster may happen on earth.
3If the clouds are full of rain,
they empty themselves on the earth,
and if a tree falls to the south or to the north,
in the place where the tree falls, there it will lie.
4He who observes the wind will not sow,
and he who regards the clouds will not reap.
5As you do not know the way the spirit comes to the bones in the womb of a woman with child, so you do not know the work of God who makes everything.
6In the morning sow your seed, and at evening withhold not your hand, for you do not know which will prosper, this or that, or whether both alike will be good.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The World Turned Upside Down</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Life is filled with risk, so choose wisdom over foolishness.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-ecclesiastes-104-20">Read: Ecclesiastes 10:4-20&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If the anger of the ruler rises against you, do not leave your place,
for calmness will lay great offenses to rest.
5There is an evil that I have seen under the sun, as it were an error proceeding from the ruler: 6folly is set in many high places, and the rich sit in a low place. 7I have seen slaves on horses, and princes walking on the ground like slaves.
8He who digs a pit will fall into it,
and a serpent will bite him who breaks through a wall.
9 He who quarries stones is hurt by them,
and he who splits logs is endangered by them.
10If the iron is blunt, and one does not sharpen the edge,
he must use more strength,
but wisdom helps one to succeed.
11If the serpent bites before it is charmed,
there is no advantage to the charmer.
12The words of a wise man’s mouth win him favor,
but the lips of a fool consume him.
13The beginning of the words of his mouth is foolishness,
and the end of his talk is evil madness.
14 A fool multiplies words,
though no man knows what is to be,
and who can tell him what will be after him?
15The toil of a fool wearies him,
for he does not know the way to the city.
16 Woe to you, O land, when your king is a child,
and your princes feast in the morning!
17Happy are you, O land, when your king is the son of the nobility,
and your princes feast at the proper time,
for strength, and not for drunkenness!
18Through sloth the roof sinks in,
and through indolence the house leaks.
19Bread is made for laughter,
and wine gladdens life,
and money answers everything.
20Even in your thoughts, do not curse the king,
nor in your bedroom curse the rich,
for a bird of the air will carry your voice,
or some winged creature tell the matter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The World Turned Upside Down - Supplement</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1-supplement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1-supplement/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="question-3">Question 3&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Listen to the talk that goes on in your home. How much of it is impatient and
unkind? How often are words spoken out of selfishness and personal
desire? How easily do outbursts of anger occur? How often do we bring up
past wrongs? How do we fail to communicate hope? How do we fail to
protect? How often do our words carry threats that we have “had it” and are
about to quit? Stop and listen, and you will see how much we need to hold
our talk to this standard of love, and how often the truth we profess to speak
has been distorted by our sin.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Meaningless: Week 12</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-8/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="making-sense-of-a-crooked-world">Making Sense of a Crooked World&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>God is not to blame for this crooked world.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read-ecclesiastes-715-29">Read: Ecclesiastes 7:15-29&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In my vain life I have seen everything. There is a righteous man who perishes in his righteousness, and there is a wicked man who prolongs his life in his evildoing. 16 Be not overly righteous, and do not make yourself too wise. Why should you destroy yourself? 17 Be not overly wicked, neither be a fool. Why should you die before your time? 18 It is good that you should take hold of this, and from that withhold not your hand, for the one who fears God shall come out from both of them. 19 Wisdom gives strength to the wise man more than ten rulers who are in a city. 20 Surely there is not a righteous man on earth who does good and never sins. 21 Do not take to heart all the things that people say, lest you hear your servant cursing you. 22 Your heart knows that many times you yourself have cursed others. 23 All this I have tested by wisdom. I said, “I will be wise,” but it was far from me. 24 That which has been is far off, and deep, very deep; who can find it out? 25 I turned my heart to know and to search out and to seek wisdom and the scheme of things, and to know the wickedness of folly and the foolishness that is madness. 26 And I find something more bitter than death: the woman whose heart is snares and nets, and whose hands are fetters. He who pleases God escapes her, but the sinner is taken by her. 27 Behold, this is what I found, says the Preacher, while adding one thing to another to find the scheme of things— 28 which my soul has sought repeatedly, but I have not found. One man among a thousand I found, but a woman among all these I have not found. 29 See, this alone I found, that God made man upright, but they have sought out many schemes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Meaningless: Week 11</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-dash-in-the-middle">The Dash in the Middle&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Life is serious business&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ecclesiastes 7:1-14&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A good name is better than precious ointment,
and the day of death than the day of birth.
2It is better to go to the house of mourning
than to go to the house of feasting,
for this is the end of all mankind,
and the living will lay it to heart.
3Sorrow is better than laughter,
for by sadness of face the heart is made glad.
4The heart of the wise is in the house of mourning,
but the heart of fools is in the house of mirth.
5It is better for a man to hear the rebuke of the wise
than to hear the song of fools.
6 For as the crackling of thorns under a pot,
so is the laughter of the fools;
this also is vanity.
7Surely oppression drives the wise into madness,
and a bribe corrupts the heart.
8Better is the end of a thing than its beginning,
and the patient in spirit is better than the proud in spirit.
9 Be not quick in your spirit to become angry,
for anger lodges in the heart of fools.
10Say not, “Why were the former days better than these?”
For it is not from wisdom that you ask this.
11Wisdom is good with an inheritance,
an advantage to those who see the sun.
12For the protection of wisdom is like the protection of money,
and the advantage of knowledge is that wisdom preserves the life of him who has it.
13Consider the work of God:
who can make straight what he has made crooked?
14 In the day of prosperity be joyful, and in the day of adversity consider: God has made the one as well as the other, so that man may not find out anything that will be after him.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Wait | Trust | Pray</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We must remind ourselves to wait and trust in God’s power, love, and justice in all circumstances rather than our own
intellect and power, because God alone is Sovereign.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="scripture-reading">Scripture reading&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Psalm 62&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>For God alone my soul waits in silence; from him comes my salvation. 2 He alone is my rock and my
salvation, my fortress; I shall not be greatly shaken. 3 How long will all of you attack a man to batter him,
like a leaning wall, a tottering fence? 4 They only plan to thrust him down from his high position. They
take pleasure in falsehood. They bless with their mouths, but inwardly they curse. Selah 5 For God alone,
O my soul, wait in silence, for my hope is from him. 6 He only is my rock and my salvation, my fortress; I
shall not be shaken. 7 On God rests my salvation and my glory; my mighty rock, my refuge is God. 8 Trust
in him at all times, O people; pour out your heart before him; God is a refuge for us. Selah 9 Those of low
estate are but a breath; those of high estate are a delusion; in the balances they go up; they are together
lighter than a breath. 10 Put no trust in extortion; set no vain hopes on robbery; if riches increase, set not
your heart on them. 11 Once God has spoken; twice have I heard this that power belongs to God, 12 and
that to you, O Lord, belongs steadfast love. For you will render to a man according to his work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Is being single better?</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/rabbit-trails/is-singleness-better/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/rabbit-trails/is-singleness-better/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Disclaimer: The opinions expressed in this article are my own and do not necessarily reflect those of CrossPointe church. As in all things, you should defer to the Word of God as the final authority and do your own research. &amp;ndash; &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Ryan&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>When it comes to being single or married, which is better? In 1 Corinthians 7 is Paul saying being single is better than being married? To find the answer to this, let&amp;rsquo;s first establish the context we are diving into.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 5</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-5/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="what-is-precious-to-jesus">What Is Precious to Jesus?&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Church is Precious to Jesus!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ephesians 5:22-32&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="discussion-questions">Discussion Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The church is called to submit to Christ, name some ways we struggle to submit
and discuss how we can better follow the headship of our Savior.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Separation and sanctification are presented together in verses 26-27. Talk about
why these two things are necessary in the life of every believer.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read verses 28-30 and explain how the text provides comfort, hope, and
encouragement. How do these verses challenge you?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Marriage has always been a picture of Jesus’ union with His church. How
should this truth impact your marriage or future marriage? Name specific
reasons we fail to follow God’s instruction for marriage?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Bonus question: How has the fall affected the roles in marriage the God laid out? Read d Genesis 3:16-17.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 4</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-4/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="week-4---the-dearest-place-on-earth">Week 4 - The Dearest Place on Earth&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We are given a charge in Matthew 28 that we refer to as the great commission. With this charge we often reflect on the evangelism aspect and sometimes forget the call given of baptizing believers, and following the commands, and teaching of Jesus. It is important to remember these teachings, and as a church to carry out the ordinances that Christ established for His bride.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 3</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-3/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="week-3---the-dearest-place-on-earth">Week 3 - The Dearest Place on Earth&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Church Membership matters for the good of believers to edify and strengthen them in their walk with Jesus and for unbelievers who will know they follow Jesus by the way they love one another.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="scripture-reading">Scripture Reading&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>1 Corinthians 12:12-20 12&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For just as the body is one and has many members, and all the members of the body, though many, are one body, so it is with Christ. 13 For in one Spirit we were all baptized into one body—Jews or Greeks, slaves or free—and all were made to drink of one Spirit. 14 For the body does not consist of one member but of many. 15 If the foot should say, “Because I am not a hand, I do not belong to the body,” that would not make it any less a part of the body. 16 And if the ear should say, “Because I am not an eye, I do not belong to the body,” that would not make it any less a part of the body. 17 If the whole body were an eye, where would be the sense of hearing? If the whole body were an ear, where would be the sense of smell? 18 But as it is, God arranged the members in the body, each one of them, as he
chose. 19 If all were a single member, where would the body be? 20 As it is, there are many parts, yet one body.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 2</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The local Church is by God’s design, the place for us to grow in the Word of God, as we commit to Him and each other, with hearts that please Him in all that we do.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="scripture-reading">Scripture reading&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Acts 2:36-47&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let all the house of Israel therefore know for certain that God has made him both Lord and Christ, this Jesus whom you crucified.” 37 Now when they heard this they were cut to the heart, and said to Peter and the rest of the apostles, “Brothers, what shall we do?” 38 And Peter said to them, “Repent and be baptized every one of you in the name of Jesus Christ for the forgiveness of your sins, and you will receive the gift of the Holy Spirit. 39 For the promise is for you and for your children and for all who are far off, everyone whom the Lord our God calls to himself.” 40 And with many other words he bore witness and continued to exhort them, saying, “Save yourselves from this crooked generation.” 41 So those who received his word were baptized, and there were added that day about three thousand souls. 42 And they devoted themselves to the apostles’ teaching and the fellowship, to the breaking of bread and the prayers. 43 And awe came upon every soul, and many wonders and signs were being done through the apostles. 44 And all who believed were together and had all things in common. 45 And they were selling their possessions and belongings and distributing the proceeds to all, as any had need. 46 And day by day, attending the temple together and breaking bread in their homes, they received their food with glad and generous hearts, 47 praising God and having favor with all the people. And the Lord added to their number day by day those who were being saved.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 1</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="big-idea">Big Idea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ekklesia simply means “those who are called out.” As the Church, we are a group of believers called out by God from slavery of sin through faith in Jesus Christ. This shapes everything that we do. Every church should be obedient to the headship of Christ and submissive to the truths that he taught.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="scripture-reading">Scripture reading&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Matthew 16:13-20&lt;/p>
&lt;p>13 Now when Jesus came into the district of Caesarea Philippi, he asked his disciples, “Who do people say that the Son of Man is?” 14 And they said, “Some say John the Baptist, others say Elijah, and others Jeremiah or one of the prophets.” 15 He said to them, “But who do you say that I am?” 16 Simon Peter replied, “You are the Christ, the Son of the living God.” 17 And Jesus answered him, “Blessed are you, Simon Bar-Jonah! For flesh and blood has not revealed this to you, but my Father who is in heaven. 18 And I tell you, you are Peter, and on this rock I will build my church, and the gates of hell shall not prevail against it. 19 I will give you the keys of the kingdom of heaven, and whatever you bind on earth shall be bound in heaven, and whatever you loose on earth shall be loosed in heaven.” 20 Then he strictly charged the disciples to tell no one that he was the Christ.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2025/winter/week-7/</guid><description>&lt;p>The God and the Faithless&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="read">Read:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bible.com/bible/59/DEU.1.ESV">Malachi 2:17 – 3:12&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="small-group-discussion">Small Group Discussion&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>In 2:17, we read that God is wearied by the people’s words. What does this reveal to us
about God?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are ways that we, too, may weary Him with what we say or do?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In 3:3, we read of Messiah purifying the sons of Levi—that is, the priests. However, in the
New Testament we read that all believers are part of the priesthood (1 Pet 2:4-5, 9-10). We,
too, should therefore expect to be purified—have our sins removed. This will be completed
when Christ returns, but God is also purifying us now. How have you experienced this in
your life? Is it painless? How can we cultivate gratefulness for this process?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Read Mal 3:6. Why is it good news that God does not change?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why was it such a big deal that the people were cutting corners on their tithe? See 3:10-12.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;ol start="2">
&lt;li>
&lt;ol start="3">
&lt;li>Repent of faithless words, actions.
Thank God that we have abundant reasons to trust Him.
Commit to speaking truthfully about God and giving generously to show you trust Him&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title/><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/prayer-tracker-old/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/prayer-tracker-old/</guid><description>&lt;div>
&lt;canvas id="myChart">&lt;/canvas>
this is another test
&lt;/div>
&lt;script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/chart.js">&lt;/script>
&lt;script>
const ctx = document.getElementById('myChart');
new Chart(ctx, {
type: 'bar',
data: {
labels: ['Red', 'Blue', 'Yellow', 'Green', 'Purple', 'Orange'],
datasets: [{
label: '# of Votes',
data: [12, 19, 3, 5, 2, 3],
borderWidth: 1
}]
},
options: {
scales: {
y: {
beginAtZero: true
}
}
}
});
&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Time Spent in Prayer</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/prayer-tracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/prayer-tracker/</guid><description>&lt;style>
@import url("https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Rubik&amp;display=swap");
:root {
--color-black: #112c34;
--color-blue-dark: #65849a;
--color-mustard-light: #ede6d9;
--color-mustard-extra-light: #fcf9ed;
--color-mustard-midtone: #9c7830;
}
#prayer-section {
width: 100%;
display: block;
}
.black {
color:black;
}
form {
direction: ltr;
right: 0;
width: 100%;
max-width: 340px;
padding: 56px 48px;
border-radius: 40px;
box-shadow: 0px 8px 40px rgba(128, 128, 128, 0.15);
display: block;
/* flex-direction: column; */
align-items: center;
background-color: #fffef9;
}
form > div {
margin-bottom: 32px;
}
form > div:last-child {
margin-bottom: 0;
}
.number-input-container {
width: 244px;
display: grid;
grid-template-columns: 48px auto 48px;
}
label {
display: inline-block;
margin-bottom: 4px;
font-size: 12px;
line-height: 24px;
letter-spacing: 2px;
text-transform: uppercase;
color: var(--color-blue-dark);
}
.number-input {
width: 100%;
display: flex;
flex-direction: row;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
overflow: hidden;
}
input[type="number"] {
-webkit-appearance: none;
-webkit-border-radius: 0px;
-moz-appearance: none;
appearance: none;
position: relative;
width: 100%;
min-width: 100%;
height: 48px;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-light);
border-left: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);
border-right: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);
border-radius: none;
font-size: 16px;
line-height: 24px;
text-align: center;
transition: all 0.2s ease-out;
}
input[type="number"]:focus {
background-color: white;
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-midtone);
outline: none;
}
input[type="number"]::-webkit-inner-spin-button,
input[type="number"]::-webkit-outer-spin-button {
-webkit-appearance: none;
margin: 0;
}
input[type="number"] {
-moz-appearance: textfield;
}
#prayer-section button {
position: relative;
height: 100%;
margin-top: 32px;
padding: 12px 16px;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-light);
border-radius: none;
transition: all 0.1s ease-out;
cursor: pointer;
-webkit-appearance: none;
-webkit-transform: scale(1);
transform: scale(1);
}
#prayer-section button {
margin: 0;
color: var(--color-black);
}
#prayer-section button:active,
button:focus {
outline: none;
}
#prayer-section button::after {
content: "";
position: absolute;
opacity: 1;
top: 0;
left: 0;
bottom: 0;
right: 0;
transition: inherit;
background-position: center;
background-repeat: no-repeat;
}
#prayer-section button:disabled {
pointer-events: none;
}
#prayer-section button:disabled::after {
opacity: 0.25;
}
#prayer-section .button-decrement::after {
background-image: url("data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg width='24' height='24' viewBox='0 0 24 24' fill='none' xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%3E%3Cpath d='M17 12H7' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3C/svg%3E%0A");
}
#prayer-section .button-increment::after {
background-image: url("data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg width='24' height='24' viewBox='0 0 24 24' fill='none' xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%3E%3Cpath d='M12 7V17' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3Cpath d='M17 12H7' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3C/svg%3E%0A");
}
#prayer-section .button-decrement {
border-right: none;
}
#prayer-section .button-increment {
border-left: none;
}
@media (hover: hover) {
input[type="number"]:hover,
#prayer-section button:hover {
background-color: white;
}
#prayer-section button:active {
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
transform: translateY(1px);
}
}
@media (hover: none) {
#prayer-section button:active {
background-color: white;
transform: translateY(1px);
}
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;div>
&lt;h3>&lt;span class="tally-display-hours">&lt;/span> hours and &lt;span class="tally-display-minutes">&lt;/span> minutes total&lt;/h3>
&lt;div id="prayer-section">
&lt;form action="javascript:void(0);">
&lt;div>
&lt;div>
&lt;label for="hue">Prayer minutes tally&lt;/label>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="number-input-container">
&lt;button
type="button"
class="button-decrement"
onclick="setNumber(event)"
data-input-id="hue"
data-operation="decrement"
>&lt;/button>
&lt;div class="number-input">
&lt;input
type="number"
id="hue"
name="hue"
class="number-input-text-box"
value="0"
min="0"
max="360"
oninput="handleNumberInput()"
onblur="handleNumberInputBlur(event)"
data-step="5"
/>
&lt;/div>
&lt;button
type="button"
class="button-increment"
onclick="setNumber(event)"
data-input-id="hue"
data-operation="increment"
>&lt;/button>
&lt;/div>
&lt;button
type="button"
onclick="addPrayerTime(event)"
>Add time&lt;/button>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/form>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2>Weekly Prayer&lt;/h2>
&lt;canvas id="weekChart">&lt;/canvas>
&lt;h2>Hours of the day&lt;/h2>
&lt;canvas id="hoursChart">&lt;/canvas>
&lt;h2>Days of the week&lt;/h2>
&lt;canvas id="daysChart">&lt;/canvas>
&lt;/div>
&lt;script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/chart.js">&lt;/script>
&lt;script src="https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/prayer.js">&lt;/script>
&lt;script>
getTimespans().then((timespans) => {
const [hoursMap, daysMap, weeklyMap] = timespans;
const endIndex = daysMap.size - 1;
const hoursChart = document.getElementById('hoursChart');
const daysChart = document.getElementById('daysChart');
const weekChart = document.getElementById('weekChart');
new Chart(weekChart, {
type: 'line',
data: {
labels: [...weeklyMap.keys()],
datasets: [{
label: 'Minutes in prayer',
data: [...weeklyMap.values()],
borderWidth: 1
}]
},
options: {
scales: {
y: {
beginAtZero: true
}
}
}
});
new Chart(hoursChart, {
type: 'bar',
data: {
labels: [...hoursMap.keys()],
datasets: [{
label: 'Minutes in prayer',
data: [...hoursMap.values()],
borderWidth: 1
}]
},
options: {
scales: {
y: {
beginAtZero: true
}
}
}
});
new Chart(daysChart, {
type: 'bar',
data: {
labels: [...daysMap.keys()],
datasets: [{
label: 'Minutes in prayer',
data: [...daysMap.values()],
borderWidth: 1
}]
},
options: {
scales: {
y: {
beginAtZero: true
}
}
}
});
}).catch(error => console.log(error));
&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Time Spent reading the Word</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/reading-tracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/reading-tracker/</guid><description>&lt;style>
@import url("https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Rubik&amp;display=swap");
:root {
--color-black: #112c34;
--color-blue-dark: #65849a;
--color-mustard-light: #ede6d9;
--color-mustard-extra-light: #fcf9ed;
--color-mustard-midtone: #9c7830;
}
#prayer-section {
width: 100%;
display: block;
}
.black {
color: black;
}
form {
direction: ltr;
right: 0;
width: 100%;
max-width: 340px;
padding: 56px 48px;
border-radius: 40px;
box-shadow: 0px 8px 40px rgba(128, 128, 128, 0.15);
display: block;
/* flex-direction: column; */
align-items: center;
background-color: #fffef9;
}
form > div {
margin-bottom: 32px;
}
form > div:last-child {
margin-bottom: 0;
}
.number-input-container {
width: 244px;
display: grid;
grid-template-columns: 48px auto 48px;
}
label {
display: inline-block;
margin-bottom: 4px;
font-size: 12px;
line-height: 24px;
letter-spacing: 2px;
text-transform: uppercase;
color: var(--color-blue-dark);
}
.number-input {
width: 100%;
display: flex;
flex-direction: row;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
overflow: hidden;
}
input[type="number"] {
-webkit-appearance: none;
-webkit-border-radius: 0px;
-moz-appearance: none;
appearance: none;
position: relative;
width: 100%;
min-width: 100%;
height: 48px;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-light);
border-left: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);
border-right: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);
border-radius: none;
font-size: 16px;
line-height: 24px;
text-align: center;
transition: all 0.2s ease-out;
}
input[type="number"]:focus {
background-color: white;
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-midtone);
outline: none;
}
input[type="number"]::-webkit-inner-spin-button,
input[type="number"]::-webkit-outer-spin-button {
-webkit-appearance: none;
margin: 0;
}
input[type="number"] {
-moz-appearance: textfield;
}
.text-green {
color: green;
}
.mt {
margin-top: 10px;
}
.mb {
margin-bottom: 20px;
}
.show {
display: block;
}
.hide {
display: none;
}
#prayer-section button {
position: relative;
height: 100%;
margin-top: 32px;
padding: 12px 16px;
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
border: 1px solid var(--color-mustard-light);
border-radius: none;
transition: all 0.1s ease-out;
cursor: pointer;
-webkit-appearance: none;
-webkit-transform: scale(1);
transform: scale(1);
}
#prayer-section button {
margin: 0;
color: var(--color-black);
}
#prayer-section button:active,
button:focus {
outline: none;
}
#prayer-section button::after {
content: "";
position: absolute;
opacity: 1;
top: 0;
left: 0;
bottom: 0;
right: 0;
transition: inherit;
background-position: center;
background-repeat: no-repeat;
}
#prayer-section button:disabled {
pointer-events: none;
}
#prayer-section button:disabled::after {
opacity: 0.25;
}
#prayer-section .button-decrement::after {
background-image: url("data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg width='24' height='24' viewBox='0 0 24 24' fill='none' xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%3E%3Cpath d='M17 12H7' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3C/svg%3E%0A");
}
#prayer-section .button-increment::after {
background-image: url("data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg width='24' height='24' viewBox='0 0 24 24' fill='none' xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%3E%3Cpath d='M12 7V17' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3Cpath d='M17 12H7' stroke='%23112C34' stroke-width='2' stroke-miterlimit='10' stroke-linecap='round' stroke-linejoin='round'/%3E%3C/svg%3E%0A");
}
#prayer-section .button-decrement {
border-right: none;
}
#prayer-section .button-increment {
border-left: none;
}
@media (hover: hover) {
input[type="number"]:hover,
#prayer-section button:hover {
background-color: white;
}
#prayer-section button:active {
background-color: var(--color-mustard-extra-light);
transform: translateY(1px);
}
}
@media (hover: none) {
#prayer-section button:active {
background-color: white;
transform: translateY(1px);
}
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;div>
&lt;h3>
&lt;span class="tally-display-hours">&lt;/span> hours and
&lt;span class="tally-display-minutes">&lt;/span> minutes total
&lt;/h3>
&lt;div class="mb">
&lt;span id="total-progress-percent">32%&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span
>&lt;progress id="total-progress" value="32" max="100">32%&lt;/progress> of
total goal
&lt;/div>
&lt;h3>
&lt;span id="tally-display-week-hours">&lt;/span> hours and
&lt;span id="tally-display-week-minutes">&lt;/span> minutes this week
&lt;/h3>
&lt;div class="mb">
&lt;span id="weekly-progress-percent">32%&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span
>&lt;progress id="weekly-progress" value="32" max="100">32%&lt;/progress> of
weekly goal
&lt;/div>
&lt;div id="prayer-section">
&lt;form action="javascript:void(0);">
&lt;div>
&lt;div>
&lt;label for="hue">Reading minutes tally&lt;/label>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="number-input-container">
&lt;button
type="button"
class="button-decrement"
onclick="setNumber(event)"
data-input-id="hue"
data-operation="decrement"
>&lt;/button>
&lt;div class="number-input">
&lt;input
type="number"
id="hue"
name="hue"
class="number-input-text-box"
value="0"
min="0"
max="360"
oninput="handleNumberInput()"
onblur="handleNumberInputBlur(event)"
data-step="5"
/>
&lt;/div>
&lt;button
type="button"
class="button-increment"
onclick="setNumber(event)"
data-input-id="hue"
data-operation="increment"
>&lt;/button>
&lt;/div>
&lt;label for="book-dropdown">Book&lt;/label>
&lt;select id="book-dropdown">
&lt;option value="Genesis">Genesis&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Exodus">Exodus&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Leviticus">Leviticus&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Numbers">Numbers&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Deuteronomy">Deuteronomy&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Joshua">Joshua&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Judges">Judges&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Ruth">Ruth&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Samuel">1 Samuel&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Samuel">2 Samuel&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Kings">1 Kings&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Kings">2 Kings&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Chronicles">1 Chronicles&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Chronicles">2 Chronicles&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Ezra">Ezra&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Nehemiah">Nehemiah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Esther">Esther&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Job">Job&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Psalms">Psalms&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Proverbs">Proverbs&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Ecclesiastes">Ecclesiastes&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Song of Solomon">Song of Solomon&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Isaiah">Isaiah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Jeremiah">Jeremiah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Lamentations">Lamentations&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Ezekiel">Ezekiel&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Daniel">Daniel&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Hosea">Hosea&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Joel">Joel&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Amos">Amos&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Obadiah">Obadiah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Jonah">Jonah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Micah">Micah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Nahum">Nahum&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Habakkuk">Habakkuk&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Zephaniah">Zephaniah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Haggai">Haggai&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Zechariah">Zechariah&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Malachi">Malachi&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Matthew">Matthew&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Mark">Mark&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Luke">Luke&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="John">John&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Acts">Acts&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Romans">Romans&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Corinthians">1 Corinthians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Corinthians">2 Corinthians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Galatians">Galatians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Ephesians">Ephesians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Philippians">Philippians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Colossians">Colossians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Thessalonians">1 Thessalonians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Thessalonians">2 Thessalonians&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Timothy">1 Timothy&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Timothy">2 Timothy&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Titus">Titus&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Philemon">Philemon&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Hebrews">Hebrews&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="James">James&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 Peter">1 Peter&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 Peter">2 Peter&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="1 John">1 John&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="2 John">2 John&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="3 John">3 John&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Jude">Jude&lt;/option>
&lt;option value="Revelation">Revelation&lt;/option>
&lt;/select>
&lt;button type="button" onclick="addTime(event)">Add time&lt;/button>
&lt;p id="success-message" class="text-green mt hide">
Reading added successfully!
&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>