<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Small Group Notes</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Small Group Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Heart of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2023/winter/week-1/</guid><description>Big Idea Seek the Lord instead of seeking after things, like those who have no hope.
Read: Matthew 6:25-34 “Therefore I tell you, do not be anxious about your life, what you will eat or what you will drink, nor about your body, what you will put on. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothing? “Therefore do not be anxious about tomorrow, for tomorrow will be anxious for itself.</description></item><item><title>The Grace of God</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-8/</guid><description>Announcements Church office is closed Wednesday and Thursday No Mid-Week Activities on Campus this week Children’s Christmas Program is December 4th Church vote on 2023 spending plan is December 4th Big Idea The grace of God is required for life and godliness.
Read: Titus 2:11-15 For the grace of God has appeared, bringing salvation for all people, 12training us to renounce ungodliness and worldly passions, and to live self-controlled, upright, and godly lives in the present age, 13waiting for our blessed hope, the appearing of the glory of our great God and Savior Jesus Christ, 14who gave himself for us to redeem us from all lawlessness and to purify for himself a people for his own possession who are zealous for good works.</description></item><item><title>More Than Knowledge</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-7/</guid><description>Announcements November 20th: Christmas Decorating after Morning Worship. November 23rd: Church offices are closed and there are no mid-week activities. Christmas Eve: Services at 4:00 and 6:00 pm. Big Idea Right teaching leads to right living which displays the truth and beauty of the gospel.
Read: Titus 2:1-10 But as for you, teach what accords with sound doctrine. 2Older men are to be sober-minded, dignified, self-controlled, sound in faith, in love, and in steadfastness.</description></item><item><title>The Men Who Must Speak &amp; The Men Who Must Be Silenced</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-6/</guid><description>Announcements Vote on Tuesday! 2023 Budget Presentation after morning worship on November 13th. Church Christmas Decorating: November 20th after morning worship. Big Idea A well-ordered church is led by elders who teach and protect God’s people.
Read: Titus 1:5-16 This is why I left you in Crete, so that you might put what remained into order, and appoint elders in every town as I directed you— 6if anyone is above reproach, the husband of one wife, and his children are believers and not open to the charge of debauchery or insubordination.</description></item><item><title>A Well-Built Life</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-5/</guid><description>Announcements Men and Women in Prayer is this Saturday at 8:30am November 6th: Lord’s Supper and Fall-Back Sunday Big Idea God can be trusted; therefore, your life can be built on who God is and what God has done.
Read: Titus 1:1-4 Discussion Questions What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week? Read vs. 1. Paul identified himself as a “servant of God and an apostle of Jesus Christ.</description></item><item><title>The End of the Matter</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-4/</guid><description>Announcements • Faith Promise Commitment Sunday is next Sunday. We will not be collecting commitment cards, but we do ask that you and your family will commit to help fund our mission efforts.
• Secure the Knot is this coming Saturday. October 23rd is the last day to register for this important event.
Big Idea Life under the sun is complex but doesn’t have to be complicated if you fear God and obey His commandments.</description></item><item><title>Rejoice and Remember</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3/</guid><description>ANNOUNCEMENTS Mission Emphasis next Sunday. Please get food truck tickets only if you’re planning to stay for the missionary presentations after lunch. Secure the Knot is Saturday, October 29. Please sign up by the end of this week—cost is $30.00 per couple and is a small but great investment in your marriage. Faith Promise Commitment Sunday is October 30. Pray about how much you will generously give to support CrossPointe’s mission program for the next 12 months.</description></item><item><title>Rejoice and Remember - Supplement</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3-supplement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-3-supplement/</guid><description>Question 3 Once again the Preacher is honest about the troubles of life, both physical and psychological. He also has some advice for us: we should do what we can to remove discouragement from our souls and to minimize damage to our bodies. This is not a call to deny the very real suffering that everyone experiences. Nor is it a call to escape pain by living for pleasure. Rather, it is a call to take care of our mental and physical health.</description></item><item><title>What You Don’t Know Can Hurt You</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-2/</guid><description>Big Idea Incomplete knowledge is not always a reason for inaction.
Read: Ecclesiastes 11:1-6 Cast your bread upon the waters, for you will find it after many days. 2 Give a portion to seven, or even to eight, for you know not what disaster may happen on earth. 3If the clouds are full of rain, they empty themselves on the earth, and if a tree falls to the south or to the north, in the place where the tree falls, there it will lie.</description></item><item><title>The World Turned Upside Down</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1/</guid><description>Big Idea Life is filled with risk, so choose wisdom over foolishness.
Read: Ecclesiastes 10:4-20 If the anger of the ruler rises against you, do not leave your place, for calmness will lay great offenses to rest. 5There is an evil that I have seen under the sun, as it were an error proceeding from the ruler: 6folly is set in many high places, and the rich sit in a low place.</description></item><item><title>The World Turned Upside Down - Supplement</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1-supplement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/autumn/week-1-supplement/</guid><description>Question 3 Listen to the talk that goes on in your home. How much of it is impatient and unkind? How often are words spoken out of selfishness and personal desire? How easily do outbursts of anger occur? How often do we bring up past wrongs? How do we fail to communicate hope? How do we fail to protect? How often do our words carry threats that we have “had it” and are about to quit?</description></item><item><title>Meaningless: Week 12</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-8/</guid><description>Making Sense of a Crooked World Big Idea God is not to blame for this crooked world.
Read: Ecclesiastes 7:15-29 In my vain life I have seen everything. There is a righteous man who perishes in his righteousness, and there is a wicked man who prolongs his life in his evildoing. 16 Be not overly righteous, and do not make yourself too wise. Why should you destroy yourself? 17 Be not overly wicked, neither be a fool.</description></item><item><title>Meaningless: Week 11</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-7/</guid><description>The Dash in the Middle Big Idea Life is serious business
Read: Ecclesiastes 7:1-14
A good name is better than precious ointment, and the day of death than the day of birth. 2It is better to go to the house of mourning than to go to the house of feasting, for this is the end of all mankind, and the living will lay it to heart. 3Sorrow is better than laughter, for by sadness of face the heart is made glad.</description></item><item><title>Wait | Trust | Pray</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-6/</guid><description>Big Idea We must remind ourselves to wait and trust in God’s power, love, and justice in all circumstances rather than our own intellect and power, because God alone is Sovereign.
Scripture reading Psalm 62
For God alone my soul waits in silence; from him comes my salvation. 2 He alone is my rock and my salvation, my fortress; I shall not be greatly shaken. 3 How long will all of you attack a man to batter him, like a leaning wall, a tottering fence?</description></item><item><title>Is being single better?</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/rabbit-trails/is-singleness-better/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/rabbit-trails/is-singleness-better/</guid><description>Disclaimer: The opinions expressed in this article are my own and do not necessarily reflect those of CrossPointe church. As in all things, you should defer to the Word of God as the final authority and do your own research. &amp;ndash; Ryan
When it comes to being single or married, which is better? In 1 Corinthians 7 is Paul saying being single is better than being married? To find the answer to this, let&amp;rsquo;s first establish the context we are diving into.</description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 5</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-5/</guid><description>What Is Precious to Jesus? Big Idea The Church is Precious to Jesus!
Read: Ephesians 5:22-32
Discussion Questions What was the most impactful thing from the text and the sermon this week? The church is called to submit to Christ, name some ways we struggle to submit and discuss how we can better follow the headship of our Savior. Separation and sanctification are presented together in verses 26-27. Talk about why these two things are necessary in the life of every believer.</description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 4</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-4/</guid><description>Week 4 - The Dearest Place on Earth Big Idea We are given a charge in Matthew 28 that we refer to as the great commission. With this charge we often reflect on the evangelism aspect and sometimes forget the call given of baptizing believers, and following the commands, and teaching of Jesus. It is important to remember these teachings, and as a church to carry out the ordinances that Christ established for His bride.</description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 3</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-3/</guid><description>Week 3 - The Dearest Place on Earth Big Idea Church Membership matters for the good of believers to edify and strengthen them in their walk with Jesus and for unbelievers who will know they follow Jesus by the way they love one another.
Scripture Reading 1 Corinthians 12:12-20 12
For just as the body is one and has many members, and all the members of the body, though many, are one body, so it is with Christ.</description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 2</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-2/</guid><description>Big Idea The local Church is by God’s design, the place for us to grow in the Word of God, as we commit to Him and each other, with hearts that please Him in all that we do.
Scripture reading Acts 2:36-47
Let all the house of Israel therefore know for certain that God has made him both Lord and Christ, this Jesus whom you crucified.” 37 Now when they heard this they were cut to the heart, and said to Peter and the rest of the apostles, “Brothers, what shall we do?</description></item><item><title>Dearest Place on Earth - Part 1</title><link>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smallgroup.carrollmedia.dev/posts/2022/summer/week-1/</guid><description>Big Idea Ekklesia simply means “those who are called out.” As the Church, we are a group of believers called out by God from slavery of sin through faith in Jesus Christ. This shapes everything that we do. Every church should be obedient to the headship of Christ and submissive to the truths that he taught.
Scripture reading Matthew 16:13-20
13 Now when Jesus came into the district of Caesarea Philippi, he asked his disciples, “Who do people say that the Son of Man is?</description></item></channel></rss>